Guide to the Sylvester Manor Archive 1649-1996 MSS 208
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Record Group II: L'Hommedieu Family
  - Series B: Ezra L'Hommedieu
    - Subseries 1: Correspondence
      - Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1800 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Jonathan Waldo, 1804 June 27 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Nath. Waldron, 1805 February 3 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Benjamin Walker, 1808 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - John Walkins, 1802 January 8 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Elijah Wampee, 1792 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - General Washington, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Charles F. Webster, 1800 March 10 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Daniel Wells, 1791 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Thomas Wells, 1788, 1800 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - John Wheeler, 1791 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Ebeneezer White, 1806 January 30 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Henry White, 1796 April 7 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Hugh White, 1784-1798 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Josiah Whitney, 1786 January 17 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Thomas Wickes, 1784 April 8 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Joseph P. Wickham, 1797, 1799 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Mattew Wickham, 1790-1792 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - William Wickham, 1766 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Thomas Wiggins, 1784 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - E. Wilkes, 1806 April 17 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Marrius Willett, 1798, 1799, 1803 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - General John Williams, 1793 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Charles Williamson and Thomas Grant, 1792 November 6 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Andrew and Frances Wilson, 1792 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Henry Wisner, 1789 July 2 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - John Woodworth [printed letter with enclosed list], 1804 October 13 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Silas Wood, 1799, 1807 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - Judge Abraham Woodhull, 1806 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Aaron Woolworth, 1789 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Benjamin Wright, 1801-1804 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Benjamin Wright and N. Brown, 1809 December 27 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - A. Yates, 1782 October 20 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - to A. Yates, 1782 October 29 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Unknown, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Unknown, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Unknown, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Subseries 2: Financial Documents and Papers
      - Receipt of Payment by Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1755 September 18 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Payment from the Estate of Benjamin L'Hommedieu to John Gould, 1756 July 8 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Promissory Note to John Gould, 1756, July 8 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Promissory Note from David Carey, 1756 September 22 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - "Samsen Poris Acompt. with Robert Barker Cv.", 1758 March (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Peter L'Hommedieu Mortage to Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1760 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Account of Money Lent to Mr. Hopson, 1760 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - "Hezeciah Indieu Acompt. with Robert Barker", 1760 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Promissory Notes: James Fanning, Robert Barker, John Ramsdel, 1761 March 3 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Receipt - Abraham Gardiner, 1761 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Account - Ezra L'Hommedieu with Sloop John Butler (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Account - William Hubbard with Gami Bayley, 1762 August 19 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Payment - David Gardiner, 1762 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Indenture Between Israel Moore and Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1762 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Bonds and Notes of Thomas Fanning, 1762-1763 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Securities Transfer from Timothy Wells, 1763 March 36 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Partial Balance Sheet, 1749-1763 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Account - Constant Havens with William Hubbard, 1763 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Robert Barker Ordered to Take Samson [Poris] Onboard Vessel, 1763 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Expenses for Seating at Southold First Parish, 1764 January 13 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Dividend Payment, 1764 March 2 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Bond - Peter L'Hommedieu to Joseph Conkling, 1764 March 21 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Receipt - Thomas Fanning, 1764 March 23 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Receipt - David Howell, 1763 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Receipt - Samuel Landon, 1764 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Indenture Between Daniel Tuthill and John Tuthill, 1764 June 6 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Samuel Griffin Bott with William Hubbard, 1764 July 17 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Promissory Note - Aaron Isaacs to William Nicoll, 1764 December 16 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Money to Be Paid, 1764 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Account - Phineas Stanton with Eunice Lamb, 1764 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Receipt - William Nicoll, 1765 March 8 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Receipt - John Hubbard from Abraham Gardnener, 1765 March 29 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - "Monies", 1765 May 30 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Receipt - Humphrey Dooey[?], 1765 May 31 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Arthur Newman and Silas Newman Bill of Sale with Platt Conklin, 1765 October 31 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Obligation of William Hubbard, Obediah Hudson and Isaac Hubbard, 1758-1765 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Account - Haris to Thomas Darking[?], 1766 January 28 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Receipt - William Hubbard for Court Expenses, 1766 May (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Payment - William Nicoll, 1766 August 19 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Account Sheet, 1767 April 16 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Receipt - Samuel Beldon, 1767 November 16 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Receipt from W. Floyd, 1767 December 3 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Bond - Paul Reeve to Nathan Penny, 1767 December 12 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Account - Ezra L'Hommedieu to Abraham Parker, 1768 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Receipt - Uriah Rogers, 1768 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Bill of Sale - John Peck, for goods, 1769 February 10 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Bond - William Havens to Renselaer Nicoll, 1769 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Bond - Jonathan Goodall to Isaac Penny, 1770 January 8 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Receipt - John Foster, 1770 March 17 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Promissory Note - Benjamin Mapses to Richard Woodhull, 1770 April 4 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - Account - William Hubbard with John Stuart, 1770 April 15 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Bill - Richard Brown, 1770 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Receipt - Parker Wickham, 1770 May (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Account - James McClure from Usher Hampton More, 1770 July 5 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Jehabod Cleveland Promise to Pay Joseph L'Hommedieu, 1770 August 27 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Moses Rolph Requesting Payment for Jury Service, 1770 September 1770 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Promise to Pay - William Rotch, 1770 November 10 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Note of Nathan Reeve, 1770 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Bond - Daniel and James Whelock Booth to William Robert Halliock, 1770 December 14 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Receipt - William Robert Halliock, 1760-1770 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Due on Joseph Wickham's Note Against William Hubbard, 1771 March 24 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Promise to Pay - John Williams to Edward Meritt, 1771 May 5 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Account - William Hubbard with Samuel Starbuck and Co., 1771 November 14 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Bill - Richard Brown, 1771 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - Account - William Hubbard with Samuel Starbuck, 1772 February 15 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Account - George Munson with William Hubbard, 1772 April 17 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Promise to Pay - Abraham Corey to Jasper Griffing, 1772 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Receipt - Alijah Corey Payment John Stuart, 1772 June (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Bond - Isaac Smith to John Russell, 1772 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Vendue at Mattatuch, 1772 September 23 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Promise to Pay - David Howell and Silvanus Howell to Stephen Howell, 1772 December 29 (Box 10, Folder 79)
      - Account - Wlliam Hubbard with John Foster, 1772 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Bill - Comfort Sands with John Vail, 1772 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - Receipt - Thomas Poole, 1772 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Mortgage - John Hubbard, 1773 May 26 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Bond - Daniel and George Magennis to Archibald Mercer and John Schenk, 1773 August 17 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Account - Thomas Hazard, 1773 November 13 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - Quit Claim - Micah Moore to Ezra L'Hommedieu; Separate Sheet with Accounting Notes, 1774 December 6 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - Bond - Nathaniel Hallny to Joseph Jacobs, 1774 February 16 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - Promise to Pay - Eliphelet Beebe to Jonathan Conkling, 1774 March 36 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - Susquehannah Company Receipts, 1762-1774 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Comfort Sands Accounts, 1774 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - Elnathan Burts Indenture with Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1775 March 31 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Daniel Wiggins Note to John Brush, 1775 October 6 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Comfort Sands Account with Benjamin, Jonathan and Jeremiah Vail, 1770-1775 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - George Herrick Account with Daniel Phoenix, 1771-1775 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Moses Mose Promise to Pay Abraham Rose, 1776 March 11 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Debora Howell and Jonathan Howell Bond to Nathan Burnet, 1776 March 28 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - Josiah Cooper Bond to John Strong, 1776 July 11 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - List of Bonds and Notes, 1763-1776 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Phineas Fanning Bond to Jacob and John Hicks, 1777 February 11 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - William Nicoll and Elkenah Conkling Promise to Pay Daniel Blatsley, 1777 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Account - Daniel and George Magennis; Daniel and George Magennis Condition of Obligation, 1773, 1777 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Receipt - William Floyd and Ezra L'Hommedieu to Comfort Sands for 1/8 Part Privateer Montgomery, 1777 July 3 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Continental Certificates Paid to Col. Fanning, 1778 April 30 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Nathaniel Jessup Bond to Silas Howell, 1778 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Amos Sofer Bond to Solomon Smith, 1779 November 27 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Sales of Certificates at Auction by Order of Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1779 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - Account with David Gelston, 1780 April 7 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - David Hawkins Bill from Fanning & Hudson, 1780 August 9 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Promise to Pay David Fanning and John Hudson, 1780 August 10 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Promise to Pay William Devall, 1780 November 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Payment of Rent to Thomas Johnson, 1780 November 21 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Clothing Order from Ezra L'Hommedieu to James Gardiner, 1781 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Receipt: Ezra L'Hommedieu to Comfort Butler, 1/16th Part of Privateer Weasel, 1781 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Bill of Sale - Comfort Butler to Ezra L'Hommedieu for 1/16th Part of Privateer Schooner Weasel, 1781 July 12 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - James Fells Promise to Pay Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1781 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Daniel Sandford Account Against Paul Sayre, 1781 November 19 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Accounts - Schooner Weasel, 1781 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - H. Johnson Promise to Pay Gilbert Fanning, 1781/1782 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Capt. Sanford Thompson Order on David Stephanus, 1782 January 10 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Joseph Everett Receipt for Bond Against James Corwin, 1782 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Daniel Reeve's Receipt, 1782 March 19 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - List of Money Received, 1782 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Stephen Corwin Bond to Nathaniel Corwin, 1782 May 30 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Richard Brown Promise to Pay Thomas Reeve, 1782 June 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Peter Hobart Promises to Pay James McClure, 1782 June 27 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - James Hallett Promises to Pay Timothy Pierce, 1782 October 7 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Zebulon Sexton Bond to Isaac Thompson, Jeffrey Smith and Epenetus Conklyn, 1782 November 19 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Account to [Nathaniel] Eels[?], 1782 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Jasper Jennings Note to Be Paid to Edward Tappan, 1783 February 20 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Nathan Haines Bond to James Downs, 1783 June 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Account with New York State, 1783 August 20 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Receipt from Richard Wescoat, 1783 September 25 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Daniel Sanford Note with Ephraim L'Hommedieu, 1783 October 15 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Elijah Hubbard Bill, 1783 November 21 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Receipt - Ezra L'Hommedieu to H. Shailer for Transportation, 1783 December 4 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Jeremiah Hedges Promise to Pay Moses Halsey, 1783 December 15 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Henry Ten Brook Bill, 1783 December 19 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - William Goldsmith Account with Isaac Peirson, 1784 February 2 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Tuthull Promise to Pay Sylvester Lester, 1784 March 20 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Isaac Stoutenburgh Receipt of Sared London, 1784 March 25 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Joshua Salmon Promise to Pay Widow Mehetable Hempsted, 1784 August 19 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Josiah Sopend Note to Nathaniel Platt, 1784 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Jeremiah Brown Promise to Pay Abraham Cook, 1784 July 31 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Samuel Jones Indenture to Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1784 September 21 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Eli and Jonathan Arnold Bond with Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1784 November 14 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Account with Colo. Lamb, 1784 November 26 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Joshua Hempsted's Bond to Benjamin Wells, 1784 December 14 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Benjamin Conkling Account, 1784 December 24 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Bonds, 1784 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Silas Wickes Bond to Ananias Carll and Zebulon Buffet, 1785 March 2 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - William Eyres Promise to Pay Isaac Liskum, 1785 March 17 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Indenture Between George Smith and Ezra Conklin, 1785 May 16 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Promise to Pay John Ingraham from Benjamin Vaille, 1785 June 1 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Account - Henry Dering to John Nelson, 1785 July 3 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - John Hulbert Account Due, 1785 July 9 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Indenture Between Jonathan Scudder and John Loyd, 1785 August 26 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - James Huller and Elizabeth Davis Bound to Thomas Wickes, 1785 October 3 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Zebulon Sexton Bond to Isaac Thompson, 1785 December 3 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Zebulon Sexton Bond to Benjah Strong, 1785 December 3 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Jonathan Ingraham Account with Nathaniel Horton, 1786 May (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Grover Glover Promissory Note, 1786 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Richard Brown Promise to Pay Henry Brown, 1786 July (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Receipt for Payment of Note with Original Note, 1786 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Mr. Hoors Note to Pay Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1786 October 14 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Memorandum of Debts Delivered to Isaac Tuthill by Ezra L'Hommedieu to Collect, 1786 December 6 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Receipt of Abraham Skinner, 1786 March 31 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - John Corwin Accounts, 1785-1786 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - Benjamin Stone Account with Nathaniel Horton, 1778-1786 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Promise to Pay Nathan Woodhull, 1787 January 16 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Indenture Between Samuel Tillitson and Jared Landon, 1787 February 9 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Received Payment for J + H Waddington, 1787 March 15 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Joseph Post Promise to Pay Stephen Howell, 1787 March 16 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Ruth Woodhull Received Certificates, 1787 March 20 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      - Receipt from John Banks, 1787 April 21 (Box 11, Folder 68)
      - Account with Tim Green, 1787 May 23 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      - Account with John Hulbert, 1787 (Box 11, Folder 70)
      - Richard Brown Bond with Henry Brown, 1787 September 6 (Box 11, Folder 71)
      - Receipt from Sloop Lively, 1787 November 7 (Box 11, Folder 72)
      - Nathaniel Fanning Note to Jonathan Conkling, 1787 November 29 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      - David Fanning's Bond, 1787 August (Box 11, Folder 74)
      - Accounts - Ruth Woodhull and New York State, 1787 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      - Receipt from Gilbert Evernghim, 1787 (Box 11, Folder 76)
      - "Taylors Bill", 1787 May 2 (Box 11, Folder 77)
      - Receipt for Henry Brand, 1787 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 78)
      - Bond from John Gardiner to Henry Hill, 1788 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 79)
      - Receipt from Bezalect Howe, 1788 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 80)
      - Account with David Gelston, 1788 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 81)
      - Account with David Gelston, 1788 April 23 (Box 11, Folder 82)
      - Grovert Glover Agreement About Sale of Hagar, 1788 April 24 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      - Receipt from John Bank, 1788 August 12 (Box 11, Folder 84)
      - Receipt of Benjamin Tallmadge, 1788 December 6 (Box 11, Folder 85)
      - Daniel Terry Promise to Pay George Beale, 1789 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 86)
      - Jonathan Raynor Bond and Mortgage, 1789 June 26 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      - Nat Gardiner Mortgage to John Parsons IV, 1789 November 16 (Box 11, Folder 88)
      - Debts Due from John Vaill, 1789 December 26 (Box 11, Folder 89)
      - Getiton and Sattomtall, 1790 January 26 (Box 11, Folder 90)
      - Accounts Between Daniel Smith and John Cleaver Symmes, 1790 February (Box 11, Folder 91)
      - Receipt of Daniel Smith, 1790 April 13 (Box 11, Folder 92)
      - Ezra L'Hommedieu Promise to Pay Hugh White, 1790 June 21 (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - David Gelston's Account with Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1790 August 13 (Box 11, Folder 94)
      - Christopher Youngs Mortgage with Daniel Foster, 1790 September 16 (Box 11, Folder 95)
      - Indenture Between Christopher Youngs and Daniel Foster, 1790 October 6 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - Edward Stevens' Deed, 1790 October 7 (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - Stephen Corwin Promise to Pay Lazarus Cleveland, 1791 February 12 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - Sales at Auction by Order of Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1791 February 24 (Box 11, Folder 99)
      - Mortgage Agreement - John and Mary Delancey and John Morgan to Michael Price, 1791 April (Box 11, Folder 100)
      - Jonathan Terry's Settlement with Creditors, 1782-1791 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - Peter Ogilive Receipt, 1792 February 2 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - Receipt from David Longworth for Advertising, 1792 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Indenture Between James Davis and Selah Strong, 1792 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Account of Wheat, 1792 June 25 (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - A Copy of the Accounts of David Gardiner's Estate as Received by Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1791-1792 (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Payment Receipt from Ezra L'Hommedieu to David Farthingham, 1793 May 23 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Account with Jeremiah Wells, 1793 July 27 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Receipt of Payment - Mr. Webb, 1793 August 7 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Receipt for Payment for 25 Nails, 1793 August 7 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - David Gelston - Sales Balance for Sugar to Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1793 October 25 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Thomas Mathus Account, 1794 March 4 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Joseph Havens Bill to Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1794 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Account and Receipt - Ezra L'Hommedieu to John Halleack, 1794 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Request for Deed from James Terry with Confirmation by Peter Booth, 1795 April 25 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Receipt from Clinton Academy, 1795 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Account with Dering and Fordham, 1795 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Accounts - Wood Cutting, Splitting, Carting, 1794-1795 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Account of the New York Agricultural Society, Samuel Jones Treasurer, 1796 February 26 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Indenture Between Ezra L'Hommedieu and Ezra Paine, 1796 March 28 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Ezra L'Hommedieu Promise to Pay Marinus Willet, 1796 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Received of Ezra L'Hommedieu Medicines for Brotherton Indians - Receipt by Thomas Eddy, 1796 April 18 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Ezra L'Hommedieu Account with T & J Swords, 1796 June 23 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Received Payment for Robert Bowne, 1796 July 28 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Bill to John Smith, 1796 July 30 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Indenture Between Ezra L'Hommedieu and Phineas King, 1796 October 20 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Ezra and John Paine Bond, 1796 December 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Receipt of David Gelston, 1796 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Abstract of the Books Kept by the Treasurer of the University, 1796 February 29 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous Receipts and Accounts, 1792-1796 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Account Agreement - Nathaniel G., 1797 February 23 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Frances Nicoll Bond, 1797 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - John Smith Account Against David Gelston and Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1797 April 29 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - General John Smith Account with North Township, 1797 April 29 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Order to Pay by Frederick Redfield, 1797 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Daniel Osborn Receipt, 1797 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Account of Francis Follet, 1797 July 5 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Account - John Bigelow to A. Partridge, 1797 August 19 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - Receipt of Mill Saw by Nathaniel Eells, 1797 August 23 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Receipt for Rum, 1797 August 26 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Receipt from A. Enos Jr., 1797 September 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Receipt for Rum Received by Benjamin Shrall, 1797 September 25 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Nathaniel Elles & Joseth Strickland Bill to Jonathan Cowen, 1797 October 27 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - John Bigalow Account with Dering, Fordham and Hodges, 1797 December 4 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Ezra L'Hommedieu Account with Dering, 1797 December (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Order to Pay by George Huntington, 1798 February 2 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - John Greene Promise to Pay Matthew Brown, Jr., 1798 February 14 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Joseph Strickland's Bill for Sawmill Work, 1798 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Receipt for Joseph Strickland, 1798 July 14 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Joesph Strickland's Order on D. Gelston, 1798 July 26 1798 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Account with Walter Nichols & Son, 1798 August 3 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Ezra L'Hommedieu Account with N.G. Ingraham, 1798 August 3 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Receipt for 100 Dollars for Joseph Strickland, 1798 August 25 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      - Joseph Strickland Receipt for Payment by Nathan Sage, 1798 September 4 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Nathan Sage Order to Pay Jonathan Cowan for Building Saw Mill, 1798 October 29 (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Nathan Sage Receipt for Payment, 1798 October 31 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - Nathan Sage Order to Pay George Huntington, 1798 October 31 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Joseph Strickland Bill Against Ezra L'Hommedieu, 1798 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Receipt from A. Enos Jr., 1798 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Nathan Sage Account, 1798 (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Bills for Saw Mill on Salmon River, 1797-1798 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Receipt for Bond Against James Carey, 1799 January 14 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Josiah Tryon Receipt for Payment, 1799 March 4 (Box 12, Folder 57)